

# **Xavier Hernandez-Martinez**

# Web Developer

(+33) 6 26 09 19 66 xhernan.martinez@gmail.com www.xhernandez.me linkedin.com/in/xavihrez github.com/XavHernandez

## **Profile**

After a 10 years career as LiveOps manager for the french iGaming market leader, I decided to move to programming through web development. Following a Full-stack bootcamp at Le Wagon Bordeaux where I obtained my certification, I am now looking for a position as a Ruby on Rails and/or JS developer. I'm product-oriented, customer centric, and eager to develop my skills. I have good soft skills, and speak a fluent English. Open to relocation.

### **Skills**

{
Ruby,
Ruby on Rails,
JavaScript ES6,
HTML5 / CSS3,
Bootstrap,
SQLite,
PostgreSQL,
Git,
Github,
Heroku,
1

### **Experience**

#### LIVE OPERATIONS MANAGER

WINAMAX | PARIS, FR | JUL 2010 - SEPT 2019

- Orchestrated launch for products and promotions with development and creative teams.
- Managed product backlog/roadmap to optimize game client and products.
- Collaborated with development teams to optimize back-office tools.
- Designed, deployed and managed full online gaming offers (schedule and money flow).

#### **ONLINE MARKETING EXECUTIVE**

WINAMAX | LONDON, UK | AUG 2009 - JUN 2010

- Coordinated with B2B providers and customer support to manage gaming events.
- Created and maintained online content materials for products, promotions and game client.
- Deployed and managed gaming offers for french online communities.

### Education

Le Wagon Bordeaux - Full Stack Web Development CODING BOOTCAMP Q2 - 2021

Kagilum / Wensei - Professional SCRUM Certification September 2020

Universite Bordeaux III - Information & Communication DUT Information & Communication Sustainable Development Option 2007 - 2008